<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>backtracked on Alter Ego 2</title>
    <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/tags/backtracked/</link>
    <description>Recent content in backtracked on Alter Ego 2</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 19:35:45 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://alterego.berlime.com/tags/backtracked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alter Ego 2</title>
      <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/alter-ego-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 19:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/alter-ego-2/</guid>
      <description>When I was 16, I launched my blog site with blogpost.com (now blogger.com).&#xA;You say why I blog? Well before this, I didn’t mange to get a hold of a computer. So what I did is, write a journal but wouldn’t call it a journal.&#xA;You see, the way I did it was to write in a ‘magazine’ look and format where there will be so called “ads” for the stuff I find interesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WP Meet Up</title>
      <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/wp-meet-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 22:56:44 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/wp-meet-up/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, here is the first backtracked post. It is a draft I created while developing this new Hugo site. Let me bring you back in time. The post date is the event date that happened. The real date that I post a backtracked blog will have a &amp;ldquo;Original Post Date:&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Original Post date: 19th March 2024&#xA;Happy new year! It&amp;rsquo;s 2024. How was 2023? I&amp;rsquo;m sure it was a blast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Agency</title>
      <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/my-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 13:08:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/my-agency/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, here is the first post that I will be sharing about my agency.&#xA;I run a web design and development agenncy. I started out small by creating a website for my wedding business. This was before the Covid-19 pandemic. My sole purpose to create a website for my wedding business is to seamlessly connect multiple providers with customers without having to communicate with me the wedding planner.&#xA;It is a system a develop and still in developing for available for public as an app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room Updates</title>
      <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/room-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:51:17 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/room-updates/</guid>
      <description>Original Post date: 13th May 2024&#xA;Ever since my late mom bought the house I currently live in, it is still in the original, unadorned state. My late mom did not opt for any renovations or even fancy decorations and pieces of furniture.&#xA;The only thing that my mom did was the kitchen cabinet and countertop which was not included when we got this house.&#xA;Oh yeah, we got it first-hand, brand new back in around 2014.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
