<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Alter Ego 2</title>
    <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Alter Ego 2</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 19:35:45 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://alterego.berlime.com/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alter Ego 2</title>
      <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/alter-ego-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 19:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/alter-ego-2/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2009 when I was 16, I launched my blog site with blogpost.com (now blogger.com).&#xA;You say why I blog? Well before this, I didn’t mange to get a hold of a computer. So what I did is, write a journal. I wouldn’t call it a journal.&#xA;You see, the way I did it was to write in a ‘magazine’ look and format where there will be so called “ads” for the stuff I find interesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WP Meet Up</title>
      <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/wp-meet-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 22:56:44 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/wp-meet-up/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, here is the first backtracked post. It is a draft I created while developing this new Hugo site. Let me bring you back in time. The post date is the event date that happened and I will indicate the real date that I post a backtracked blog.&#xA;Post date: 19th March 2024&#xA;Happy new year! It&amp;rsquo;s 2024. How was 2023? I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;s a blast. I want to share something exciting for this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room Updates</title>
      <link>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/room-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:51:17 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/room-updates/</guid>
      <description>You see ever since my late mom got this house, it is still in the current vanilla state. My late mom did not opt for any renovations or even fancy decorations and pieces of furniture.&#xA;The only thing that my mom did is the kitchen cabinet and countertop which did not come included when we got this house.&#xA;Oh yeah, we got it first-hand, brand new back in around 2014.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
